signalhq.com 2013-05-13

# None

The following Privacy Statement (“Statement”) sets forth the policies for, the collection and use of personally identifiable information (“Information”) by Message Mediums, LLC, DBA Signal (“Signal”). This Statement covers the operation of its Web Site[ http://www.signalhq.com](http://www.signalhq.com/) (the “Site”) and its private label services, operated on behalf of third parties (its “Customers”) and supersedes any previous statement of such policies. (The Site and private label service, are referred to collectively as the “Business” in this Statement.) Signal takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure Customers are fully informed about the Information they are providing. “Personally identifiable Information” refers to information that can identify an individual such as a name, or email address. 

Signal has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.signalhq.com and does not cover information that may be collected behind the log in on our website. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@signalhq.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can [contact TRUSTe here.](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

## Collection of Information

We collect personal information on the Site to facilitate the services offered to you during your use of the business. Customers must register an account on the Site prior to having access to any of the services. To register an account on the Site, we require name, email and physical address information, as well as sensitive financial information including credit card numbers to process the registration. Where applicable, we also collect third party personal information if the registered administrator is different from the initiator of the registration for the service. By registering for the service, the platform exists for Customers to enter third party personal information as described above into their account user list. None of this personal information is used for any promotional purposes, or shared with third parties for their promotional purposes. Signal may also collect non-personally identifiable information from Customers via “cookies” (small text files placed by Signal on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called “Web beacons”), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. We also receive website navigational information such as IP address and referring URL when our Site is visited. Such information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties in aggregated, non-personally identifiable form. To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may utilize cookies, or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information. Signal is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked.

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit.  Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.  Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.  To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here:

<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118>

## No Collection of Information from Children

This Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does Signal knowingly collect, or retain Information from children under the age of 13.

## Use of Information

Signal uses Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways:

  1. To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Site.
  2. To improve the user experience with the Sites
  3. In connection with the operation of the Sites
  4. For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by Signal.

## Security

Signal utilizes industry accepted electronic and physical standards of security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage. We employ the use of SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology to protect your sensitive information during transmission. While we take every precaution to guarantee safety, no method of security is 100% effective and we encourage you to employ discretion while submitting your information.

## Information Sharing

Signal may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or to third parties under certain circumstances, such as illegal activity on our Site. Signal reserves the right to release personal information to its service providers, law enforcement, or other government officials, or in response to a formal request in a civil action, Court order or judicial proceeding as we, in our sole and absolute discretion, deems necessary or appropriate. Moreover, in the event of a merger, sale, or acquisition of some, or all of Signal’s assets, your personal information could be part of the transferred assets. In such an event, we shall notify you by a notice on the home page. Any changes to the information practices governing your information & your choices would be noted. The Site employs the use of a third party payment processor to process payments made to us. This third party is not authorized to utilize this information for any purposes beyond facilitating this service on our behalf. We post customer testimonials on our Site that may include a user’s name. We obtain permission of our Customers’ prior to posting their testimonials on our Site. When you select to comment on a blog post, please be aware that any personal information you submit therein shall be available publicly to other users of the Site & can be used to send unsolicited messages. Signal is not responsible for the personal information a user selects to disclose in a public forum. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@signalhq.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Opting Out from Offers from Signal

You will be added to Signal email newsletter list only if you register to receive newsletters via a form on the Signal website. You may opt-out of receiving our newsletters by clicking on the opt-out link included in every email newsletter we send, or by contacting privacy@signalhq.com. Signal service offerings include acting as a service provider for Customers in providing an “opt-out” platform for their end users. At any time, end users may discontinue receiving SMS offers by sending the SMS message “STOP ALL” to the applicable shortcode. Signal or its Customers shall provide end users with a subsequent SMS message confirming the discontinuance. Additionally, end users may discontinue receiving offers from a particular Customer by sending the SMS message STOP to that Customer’s particular shortcode, or by following other instructions provided by that Customer. Opting out from a particular Customer’s offers will not apply to any communications from other Customers. All information provided to the Customers is owned by said Customer and subject to its privacy statement. We are not responsible for their privacy practices during our role as the Customers’ service provider.

## Access to Information

All Customers who provide their Information to Signal may modify, correct and delete such Information by e-mailing us at support@signalhq.com and registered Customers can modify and delete their personal information and accounts by logging into their accounts on our home page and modifying their preferences.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Signal who are California residents to request certain information regarding Signal's disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: support@signalhq.com.

## Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Signal. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Signal reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time, and will reasonably notify you of such changes via system notification upon login. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information.

## Contacting Us

You can contact Signal with your questions and concerns via email (support@signalhq.com) or mail (Signal, 656 W Randolph St, Suite 4W, Chicago, IL 60661)

Effective: October 22, 2012
